Viewers all over the world, we bless your way.
Let His name be blessed.
You said, "Come unto Me, all ye that labour".
We are here, Lord.
Restore our dignity, Lord!
Restore our dominion, Lord!
Thy kingdom come;
Thy will be done.
Lord, restore our dominion!
Restore our dominion!
When your dominion is restored, you can stand any challenge.
Who is satan, devil or evil spirit when your dominion is restored?
Every spirit that stands against you, open your lips and begin to rebuke it right now.
Thy kingdom come;
Thy will be done.
My dominion - I stand right now, challenging you, satan!
Every thought of depression, being downcast - now and tomorrow, worry - now and future,
command them out!
In the name of Jesus!
Viewers, you are released, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever the enemy of your soul might have used - whatever medium, whatever chain -
it could be sickness, poverty, hardship or failure -
whatever chain the enemy of your soul might have used, to connect you to himself,
be released, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see you being released!
I can see your career being released!
I can see your finances being released!
I can see your business being released!
I can see your marriage being released!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can sense your release!
Rejoice!
I sense your release!